[
    {
      "question": "Which artist is known for coining the term 'Surrealism'?",
      "option1": "Pablo Picasso",
      "option2":"Salvador Dali",
      "option3":"Vincent Van Gogh",
      "option4":"Henri Matisse",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
    
      "question": "Which movement is associated with the use of abstract forms and shapes in art?",
      "option1": "Impressionism", 
      "option2":"Expressionism",
      "option3": "Futurism",
      "option4": "Cubism",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
    
      "question": "Which artist is known for painting the work 'The Persistence of Memory'?",
      "option1": "Pablo Picasso",
      "option2": "Salvador Dali", 
      "option3":"Vincent van Gogh",
      "option4": "Henri Matisse",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which artist is known for creating the painting 'The Scream'?",
      "option1": "Vincent van Gogh", 
      "option2":"Salvador Dali",
      "option3": "Edvard Munch", 
      "option4":"Claude Monet",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "What movement was associated with the use of bold, bright colors and thick brushstrokes?",
      "option1": "Impressionism", 
      "option2" :"Expressionism", 
      "option3":"Fauvism",
      "option4": "Cubism",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
    
      "question": "What movement was associated with the use of bright colors, simplified forms, and a focus on movement and speed",
      "option1": "Impressionism",
      "option2": "Futurism",
      "option3": "Surrealism",
      "option4": "Abstract Expressionism",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which artist is known for creating the painting 'Water Lilies'?",
      "option1": "Claude Monet",
      "option2": "Paul Cezanne",
      "option3": "Paul Gauguin",
      "option4": "Paul Klee",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which artist is known for creating the painting 'Les Demoiselles d'Avignon'?",
      "option1": "Henri Matisse",
      "option2": "Vincent van Gogh",
      "option3": "Salvador Dali",
      "option4": "Pablo Picasso",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Which artist is known for creating the painting 'Guernica'?",
      "option1": "Claude Mone",
      "option2": "Paul Cezanne",
      "option3": "Pablo Picasso",
      "option4": "Vincent van Gogh",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Which artist is known for creating the sculpture 'The Thinker'?",
      "option1": "Auguste Rodin",
      "option2": "Alexander Calder",
      "option3": "Jean Arp",
      "option4": "Henry Moore",
      "answer": 1
    }
  ]

  